This is my first time.
Yeah.
So I walk in.
I have them take a picture with this a bit and then I reveal?
Yes.
Okay, got it.
Yeah, right when you know the sweetest spot, the sweetest moment where you know the
camera is like focused.
Okay.
Hi, folk.
This is Lisa and welcome to my final fitting for the Met Gala.
Come on.
I'm super nervous.
I mean, this is my first Met.
Today I'm wearing Louis Vuitton by Pharrell.
It's recreated an artwork by Hendry Taylor.
It's crazy.
You have to see all the details.
Like, can you zoom in?
Like, you can see like the LV logo, also his art.
I fall in love with this right away But we were like trying to playing
around like which silhouette should I go with I could wear pants But do we
want to do that or you know, like do we want to make something more
crazier more fun?
And then this is what we decide And also with the color as well like
should we go with red or white when i wear black i feel powerful and
just like the perfect fit when i do the first fitting i try a lot
of like accessory like where should i put like a brooch here or necklace but
we ended up put it here because i feel like when i see men's wear
they always have like a chain belt or chain pants.
So I feel like if this look is a little too feminine, like too girly,
I think I should put this so it's make more cooler.
Also the bag, my favorite color is yellow, but I don't think yellow would be
perfect for this look.
So I chose the black and the pearl, more chic.
I'm thinking of like, should I just tie my hair up so they can really
see all the details here, or I just like put it down.
I really have fun like getting ready, like from the outfit, glam.
I always have like a long chat with my glam team.
I do a Korean face mask.
It's like, it's the must.
The night before the big event like this, I always do that.
Awesome!
Hello!
How are you?
Amazing.
Listen, super sharp.
Of course, you know, we snatched the hell out of it.
And I think that you should play the jacket for a little bit, but then
at a certain point, then you hit them with the reveal so they can really
see how snatched it is.
Okay.
It serves as a curtain.
You know what I mean?
It's like so they can see the main attraction because they have no idea that
it's going to be fitted the way it is.
This was made just for you.
Obviously, the detail of like all the Henry Taylor embroidery along with the crystals.
Crazy.
And upon your request, we put more crystals.
I want to be, you know, like it's a mat.
You know, for your first mat and moving forward, I think you just stand in
the confidence of knowing that you are eating the carpet up tonight.
It doesn't matter whether you're standing like this or you're standing like that or you're
standing whatever way you want to It's just gonna work because this was made for
you.
So i'm just gonna Yeah, like that.
Yeah And I just want to make sure the camera is understanding The level here
because my whole vibe is like predicated on three things chic wearable and
well-made you're wearing art yes i'm wearing art yeah this is crazy this look is
inspired by the theme of this year's met gala which is super fine the idea
that like you know we love this color black and the world loves the color
black they love black clothes they love black shoes they like black dresses, they like
black glasses, they like black cars, black planes, even black pink, right?
But here's a moment where we highlight the taste level and the taste buds of
black people.
I feel so honored and this is so special.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
It's great.
Can you give them a 360 and twirl.
Sure.
Good night.
I mean, like, I don't really wear this a lot.
So, you know, like for my fans or like people who love fashion, I think
they're gonna be surprised.
Bye, bub.
Okay.
Oh.
Cute.
I'm ready.
you